Contact

nphinazee@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/natoshaphinazee-91826946 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Meditech Hospitals Nursing

Natosha Phinazee

Travel Registered Nurse at WellStar Health System Greater Atlanta Area

Summary

Experienced Travel Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Emergency Medicine, Medication Administration, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), and Acute Care.

Experience

WellStar Health System
Travel Registered Nurse
May 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months)
Wellstar Cobb

American Heart Association
Certified Instructor
September 2015 - Present (4 years 10 months)
BLS, ACLS & PALS Instructor

Grady Health System Travel Registered Nurse February 2019 - April 2019 (3 months) Atlanta, Georgia

Rockdale Medical Travel RN 2018 - February 2019 (1 year)

Executed care and treatment for patients according to MD orders Educated patients on diagnosis and treatment of current condition Educated patients on prevention and care

Piedmont Walton Travel RN August 2018 - November 2018 (4 months) Monroe, GA

HCA North Florida Division Travel RN July 2016 - August 2018 (2 years 2 months)

Macon, Georgia Area

Emory Johns Creek Hospital
Travel RN
August 2016 - December 2016 (5 months)

North Fulton Medical Travel RN May 2016 - August 2016 (4 months)

Travel RN/Emergency Room

Executed care and treatment for patients according to MD orders.

Educated patients on diagnosis and treatment of current condition.

Educated patients on prevention and care.

Cartersville Medical Ctr Travel RN February 2016 - May 2016 (4 months)

Travel RN/Emergency Room

Executed care and treatment for patients according to MD orders.

Educated patients on diagnosis and treatment of current condition.

Educated patients on prevention and care.

Eastside Medical
Travel RN
September 2012 - January 2016 (3 years 5 months)
Snellville, GA

Executed care and treatment for patients according to MD orders. Educated patients on diagnosis and treatment of current condition. Educated patients on prevention and care.

Newton Memorial Hospital Travel RN May 2012 - September 2012 (5 months) Covington, GA

Executed care and treatment for patients according to MD orders.

Educated patients on diagnosis and treatment of current condition.

Educated patients on prevention and care.

WVUH
Travel RN
March 2012 - May 2012 (3 months)

Martinsburg, WV

Executed care and treatment for patients according to MD orders.

Educated patients on diagnosis and treatment of current condition.

Educated patients on prevention and care.

Palmyra Medical Charge/Staff Nurse ER and CCU 2008 - 2011 (3 years) Emergency Room

Executed care and treatment for patients according to MD orders.

Educated patients on diagnosis and treatment of current condition.

Educated patients on prevention and care.

Handled the tasks of supervising staff and conduct trainings for new nurses

Palmyra Medical Center Charge Nurse/Staff Nurse Medical Surgical April 2007 - December 2008 (1 year 9 months)

Assessed patients' status and provided pre/post-operative care.

Executed care and treatment for patients according to MD orders.

Educated patients on diagnosis and treatment of current condition.

Educated patients on prevention and care.

Phoebe Putney Memorial Hospital Staff Nurse OB/GYN May 2002 - August 2007 (5 years 4 months) Phoebe Putney Memorial

Educated patients regarding care of self, newborns, medications and treatment.

Assessed patients' pre and post operatively, notifying physicians of significant changes.

Assessed newborns and observing for significant change in status.

Promoted healthy bond between infant and mother.; Staff Nurse Labor and Delivery

Oriented patients to laboring process.

Monitored patients throughout delivery ensuring a safe birthing experience for mother and infant.

Educated patients regarding possible outcomes of procedures and side effects of medications.

Education

Darton College

Associate, Nursing · (2000 - 2002)

Albany State University

B.S. Allied, Health Science · (1992 - 1997)